YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
更多原创字幕翻译 请登陆www.YYeTs.com
■
时间轴：   YY
后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
■
翻译： vero  非燕  一块二  YY
后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
■
校对： YY    后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
老爸老妈浪漫史
第六季  第二十三集
孩子们  这是一个关于里程碑的故事
Kids, this is a story of landmarks.
人生中总会有一些时刻  让你不得不决定
There are certain moments in life when you have to decide
哪些事物你可以强忍它被拆毁的痛楚
which things you can stand to see torn down,
而哪些事物  你坚持要保留
and which things you have to preserve,
赴汤蹈火在所不惜
no matter what.
2011年5月  在纽约城市地标保护委员会
Such a moment came for all of us in May of 2011,
一次特殊会议上
at a special meeting of
我们所有人都面临着这样一刻
the New York City Landmarks Preservation Commission,
因为阿卡迪亚的命运
where the fate of The Arcadian
将就此宣判
would be decided once and for all.
阿卡迪亚的石狮
A symbol of strength and constancy,
是力量与忠诚的象征
the stone lion of The Arcadian
它已经见证了几代纽约人的成长
has watched over New Yorkers for generations.
所以请记住
So remember:
如果石狮头象征着帝王风范
if the lion head stonework is regal,
那么拆毁它  实属目无王法
then tearing it down should be illegal.
你们喜欢这么说  那好
Did you like that? All right, uh...
我们必须确保  石狮永存
We must make sure the lion is always there.
想毁了阿卡迪亚
Destroy The Arcadian?
不  量你没胆
Oh, no, don't you dare.
怎么样  怎么样  好
Yeah? Yeah? Okay.
再听这句试试
Try this one on for size...
如果想让纽约的历史发展如你所愿
If you want New York's history at your beck and call...
好了  谢谢你  艾瑞克森先生
All right, thank you, Mr. Eriksen.
我快说完了
I just have...
我们现在要听取国家巨人银行大楼
We will now hear from the architect
工程提案的建筑师
of the proposed GNB Tower,
泰德・莫斯比的陈述
Ted Mosby.
现在
Now, uh,
莫斯比先生  我们直奔主题吧
Mr. Mosby, let's just cut right to the chase.
你认为阿卡迪亚该成为地标建筑吗
Do you think The Arcadian should be a landmark?
好吧  我受不了了
Okay, it's killing me.
和"如你所愿"押韵的下句是什么
What rhymes with "beck and call?"
毁灭大球
Wrecking ball.
别去挥舞毁灭大球
Don't go swinging no wrecking ball.
谢谢你
Thank you.
莫斯比先生
Mr. Mosby,
你认为阿卡迪亚该成为地标建筑吗
do you think The Arcadian should be a landmark?
这问题不难
It's not a difficult question.
这问题其实很难
It was a difficult question.
当然  如果他早几天问我
Of course, had he asked me a few days earlier,
我会毫不犹豫地回答
I would have immediately said...
"当然  阿卡迪亚应该成为地标建筑"
"Yes. The Arcadian should be a landmark."
两天前
然后群众一片沸腾  "天啊"
And then the crowd gasps: "Oh, my God!
"他真这么说了吗"
"Did he really just say that?
"我的老天爷"
"Oh, heavens!"
"我的上帝"
"Oh, my stars!"
"我要护好我的珍珠项链"[形容格外激动]
"I must clutch my pearls!"
这么说  与会的都是些南方老妇人吗
So these things are generally attended by old Southern ladies?
差不多吧  但我的观点是
Almost exclusively. But here's my point:
如果他们问巨人银行的总建筑师  也就是本人
If they ask GNB's chief architect-- aka me--
阿卡迪亚该不该成为地标建筑
if The Arcadian should be a landmark,
而我说"应该"的话
and I say "yes"?
错了  这不是形容阿卡迪亚被摧毁的样子
That, no, that wasn't The Arcadian being destroyed;
是巨人银行摧毁阿卡迪亚希望破灭的样子
that was GNB's hopes of destroying The Arcadian.
-抱歉  我应该表达得更清楚点  -没事
- I'm sorry, I should have been more clear. - Yeah.
阿卡迪亚一定会是这样
The Arcadian's gonna be all like...
没错
Nice.
我来给巴尼传口信
I have a message from Barney.
近来巴尼与我们其他人的关系
Things between Barney and the rest of us
有点僵持不下
had gotten a little frosty.
一开始  祸起萧墙
First this happened.
见见我为阿卡迪亚新聘请的律师吧
Meet the new lawyer I hired to help save The Arcadian.
紧接着  祸不单行
And then this happened.
什么样的人渣才会
What kind of dirtbag
背弃自己最好的朋友  却反过来
doesn't stand by his best friends, but instead,
支持一个为了一件毫无意义的事情
sides with some self-righteous bitch
整天拿着扩音器瞎吼  自以为是的贱货
with a pointless cause and a megaphone?!
伙计
Dude!
你说的可是我的女朋友
That's my girlfriend.
而你知道吗
And ya know what?
我现在也支持她
I'm on her side now, too.
于是祸及池鱼
Which led to this happening.
巴尼的口信  这是要让我回避吧
Message from Barney? That's my cue to leave.
晚安  各位
Good night, guys.
-我爱你  -我也爱你
- I love you. Mmm. - Love you, too.
-晚安  -晚安
- Good night. - Good night.
好了  什么口信
All right, what's the message?
因为如果又是一幅关于我胸部
'Cause if it's another hypothetical
虚构却出奇地精确的绘图
yet eerily accurate drawing of my boobs...
对了  那个我也带来了
Yeah, I have that, too.
该死
Damn it.
好了  口信是这样的
All right, here's the message.
各位好啊  没看到你们在这儿
"Oh, hey, guys. Didn't see you there.
我忙于沉浸在自己良好的感觉中
"I was too busy feelin' fine and..."
真的吗
Really?
沉浸于良好的感觉中  而且风流快活
"Feelin' fine and gettin' some 'jine."
你们可能注意到我面前
"You may have noticed the giant plate
这一大盘鸡翅了
"of hot wings in front of me.
我知道你们有多爱吃鸡翅
"I know how much you love hot wings.
不过有人刚贿赂了厨房
"Too bad someone bribed the kitchen
让他们今晚把这道菜取消
"to take them off the menu tonight.
所以  想吃鸡翅
"So, if you want some,
就得重回巨人银行的怀抱
"you're going to have to come back to GNB.
但是要抓紧  这提议
"But hurry, this offer
转瞬即逝
"will be gone lickety-split."
邪恶地大笑
"Do evil laugh."
你们这群混蛋最近忙啥呢
So, what are you turds up to?
我们两天后要去参加地标保护委员会的会议
Oh, we've got the big LPC meeting in two days.
我的演讲已经准备好了
I have my whole presentation worked out.
我只需想一个好的押韵结尾
I just need to find a good rhyme to end on.
为什么非要押韵
Why does it need to rhyme?
如果论辩以押韵结尾
Mm. If you end an argument with a rhyme,
-说服力持久有效  -没错
- it's convincing all the time. - Yeah.
所以我们家的口号是
It's why in our apartment:
想要自己加分多多
If you're a-hopin' to score,
袜子不能随便丢丢
don't leave your socks on the floor.
-她从此没乱丢过  -对
- And she hasn't since. - No.
好吧  好吧  说几件事
Okay, okay. A couple of things.
-莉莉  我画得怎么样  -绝了
- Lily, how'd I do? - Nailed it.
其次  泰德
Secondly, Ted,
我很抱歉我对苏伊说了过分的话
I'm sorry I said mean things about Zoey.
你真的打算将这个工程弃之不顾
Are you really going to walk away from this project
就因为生我的气吗
just because you're mad at me?
这不是因为我生你的气
It's not because I'm mad at you.
巴尼  阿卡迪亚是一个叫做
Barney, The Arcadian was designed
约翰・克里福德・拉拉比的人设计的
by a guy named John Clifford Larrabee.
即使他已经去世半个世纪了
And even though he's been dead for half a century,
但我有责任  对设计先辈的责任感
it's my duty, architect to architect,
让他的作品长存于世
to keep his work alive.
告诉我你多少能理解一点吧
Please tell me a little part of you understands.
我理解
I understand.
-苏伊有魔力私处  -什么
- Zoey has magic lady bits. - What?
苏伊的私处
Zoey's lady bits...
有魔力  因此她能控制你的意识
are magic, and that's how she controls your mind.
肮几十万年
You see, every few hundred millennia,
女人的私处就有质的飞跃...
lady bits leap forward...
我知道你才刚开头
I know you're only just getting started,
可已经很恶心了
but this is already gross.
我曾遇到一个女孩
I once knew such a girl.
正是在这间酒吧
It was last call.
当时快打烊了
In this very bar.
我擦咧
What...?!
坑爹啊
No...
我擦咧
What?!
你妹啊
No...
我擦咧闹不住妞
What?!
谢谢你没提那个女孩的名字
Thank you for, um, not using a first name in that story.
巴尼  这事关乎大楼存亡
Barney, this is about the building.
别装了  明显是你被女色所迷
Come on. This is so about the girl.
好吧  我承认  是因为女人
Okay, fine. It's about the girl!
我之所以这么做是因为苏伊
I am doing this for Zoey!
我爱上她了
I'm in love with her.
我知道现在还为时过早  但很有可能
Look, I know it's early, but there's a very good chance
苏伊会是孕育我孩子的母亲
Zoey might be the mother of my children.
所以除了为捍卫约翰・克里福德・拉拉比的杰作
So, in addition to doing this for John Clifford Larrabee,
我这么做还为了卢克和莱亚
I'm also doing this for Luke and Leia.
等等  孩子取名卢克和莱亚  她会同意吗
Wait. She's gonna let you name your kids Luke and Leia?
如果我不推倒她最爱的大楼  就有可能
Not if I knock down her favorite building, she isn't.
巴尼  很抱歉
Barney, I'm sorry.
你现在才不感到抱歉呢  泰德・莫斯比
Oh, you're not sorry now, Ted Mosby.
可你以后会的
But you will be.
你会  后悔  不已
You... will... be.
那才是邪恶之笑的正版
That's how you do an evil laugh.
暂别啦
Ciao for now.
孩子们  你们还记得亚瑟・赫伯斯吗
Now, kids, you remember Arthur Hobbs,
他是巴尼和马修在巨人银行的老上司
Barney and Marshall's old boss at GNB?
亚瑟那时正在办离婚
Well, Arthur was going through a divorce
-正值伤心时期  -你好  亚瑟
- and taking it kind of hard. - Hi, Arthur.
一切顺利吧
Everything okay?
不  事事不顺
No, everything's not okay.
我那蠢妻子获得了小拖船的抚养权
My stupid wife got custody of Tugboat.
老天爷  我真该把她藏在
God, I should have kept her hidden
地下室的笼子里
in a cage in the basement.
那是不是虐畜罪吗
Isn't that animal cruelty?
我说的是藏我的妻子
I'm talking about my wife.
那没问题
Oh. That's fine, then.
是这样的  你认识那个叫泰德的设计师吧
So listen, you know Ted, the architect?
对  我认识你的朋友泰德
Yeah,I know your friend Ted.
那如果泰德在明天的重要会议上发言
So, if Ted stood up at that big meeting tomorrow
说他认为阿卡迪亚酒店应该成为地标建筑
and said that he thought The Arcadian should be a landmark...
你不会就炒他鱿鱼  对吧
you wouldn't just fire him, would you?
对吗
Right?
你不会就
You wouldn't just...
你不会的  对吧
You wouldn't just... yeah...
不  巴尼  我不会光炒他鱿鱼
No, Barney. I wouldn't just fire him.
我还要炒了你
I'd also fire you.
我去买块大软糖  咱们再谈过
Come again for Big Fudge?
你能相信吗
Can you believe that?!
我不能被解雇  罗宾
I can't be unemployed, Robin!
我的工作是我身份的象征  是我存在的意义
My job is my identity; It's who I am.
它让我有信心去说服女孩子们
It gives me the confidence I need
我是个战斗机飞行员
to convince girls I'm a fighter pilot.
我不明白
I-I don't understand.
他为什么要连你一起炒
Why would he fire you?
我不明白
I don't understand.
你为什么要连我一起炒
Why would you fire me?
你还记得莫斯比是如何得到那份工作的吗
Have you already forgotten how Mosby got that job?
因为他是我们能找到的最好的设计师
By being the best architect available?
错
No.
因为他是拉丁裔
By... being Latino?
错  我来帮你场景重现
No. Let me refresh your memory.
你当时就在这间房间
We were in this very room.
伙计们  告诉你们
Guys, I'm telling you,
如果泰德・莫斯比不令人称好  就解雇我吧
if Ted Mosby isn't fantastic, fire me.
该死
Damn it!
我开玩笑的吧
I was kidding?
我没开玩笑
I'm not kidding!
对了  亚瑟
Oh, by the way, Arthur,
你和你妻子关系怎么样
uh, how are things with you and your wife?
非常好
Really good.
实际上  我把我名下所有资产都转到了她名下
In fact, I just put all my assets in her name.
这是我迄今为止最明智的举措
Smartest thing I've ever done.
该死
Damn it!
不行  你得保证莫斯比明天别出岔子
No,you'd better make sure Mosby doesn't screw up tomorrow.
因为要么那栋大楼玩完
Because either that building is going down,
要么你玩完
or you're going down.
他们要解雇他吗  太过分了
They're going to fire him? That sucks.
他爱那份工作
He loves that job.
他都干了好多年了
And he's been doing it for years.
好吧  巴尼在巨人银行具体做什么工作
Okay, what does Barney do at GNB?
-不清楚  -他有好多房间的钥匙
- No idea. - He has a lot of keys.
好吧  泰德  你能不能先考虑下
Okay, Ted, can you just please think about this before you...
没什么好考虑的
There's nothing to think about.
我不能失去苏伊
I-I can't lose Zoey.
我现在只在乎这点
That's the only thing that matters to me right now.
好  泰德
Okay, Ted...
你知道我很喜欢苏伊
you know I love Zoey.
可有时候
But, look, sometimes...
当我去公园下棋时
I go play chess in the park.
下棋的要领...
And the key to chess...
好吧  我在网上下的
Okay, I play online.
下棋的要领是
But the key to chess...
好吧  我玩的是"愤怒的小鸟"
Okay, it's Angry Birds!
可玩"愤怒的小鸟"的要领在于
But the key to Angry Birds
总要预见到每一种可能的结果
is to always try to see every possible outcome.
要用石头或别的去砸那些猪
And to... hit some pigs with rocks or something.
我不知道  没玩过
I don't know; I don't play.
我下载不了
I can't get it to download.
重点是  你和苏伊的爱情
The point is, this thing with you and Zoey?
我可以预见三种可能性
I can see it going three possible ways.
脚本一
There's the first scenario.
委员会会长问你
The chairman asks you...
你认为阿卡迪亚该成为地标建筑吗
Do you think The Arcadian should be a landmark?
-于是你回答  -不该
- You say...- No.
然后苏伊当场跟你说分手
And Zoey dumps you on the spot.
我们分道扬镳
We're done here.
脚本二
There's the second scenario.
委员会会长问你
The chairman asks you...
你认为阿卡迪亚该成为地标建筑吗
Do you think The Arcadian should be a landmark?
-于是你回答  -该
- You say... - Yes.
然后你高兴了  大概一秒钟
And you're happy for, like, a second,
随即你意识到  你帮忙拯救的这栋大楼
until you realize the building you helped save
变成了一块纪念碑
has just become a monument
纪念这个女人害你所放弃的一切
to everything this woman made you give up,
然后你因此而恨她
and you resent her for it,
以至于到头来  你变成了那个说分手的人
so much so, in fact, that you dump her.
我们恩断义绝
We're done here.
-你说还有脚本三  -没错
- You said there was a third scenario. - Right.
委员会会长问你
The chairman asks you...
你认为阿卡迪亚该成为地标建筑吗
Do you think The Arcadian should be a landmark?
就在你作答之前
But before you can answer...
你被忍者扔出的飞镖击中脖子
You're hit in the neck with a blow dart fired by the ninja
那是苏伊前夫派来暗杀你的
Zoey's ex-husband hired to assassinate you.
我们到此为止
这个情况可能性比较小
That one's less likely.
我想说的是
What I'm saying...
我最不想说的话
what I hate saying...
听好了
is this.
你和苏伊迟早都要分手
You and Zoey are gonna break up.
但你仍旧可以挽回你和巴尼的事业
But you can still save your career and Barney's.
听我说  首先
Okay, first of all,
没有忍者能偷袭到我
no ninja's getting a jump on me.
我的反应能力有如丛林[jungle hunter 丛林猎人]
I have the reflexes of a jungle...
呆木
Tree?
其次
Second of all,
我不在乎我们会不会成功地走到一起
I don't care that the odds are stacked against us.
我宁愿试着和苏伊一起努力
I'd rather try to make this work with Zoey
也不愿意我的余生独自一人
than spend the rest of my life alone
靠玩"愤怒的小鸟"过日  话说这个游戏
playing Angry Birds, which, by the way,
我已经教你下载了不下20遍了
I've shown you how to download,like, 20 times.
我不得不说  泰德说得对
I've got to say,I'm with Ted on this.
-感谢支持  -我承认
- Thank you. - I mean, yes,
他们之间有一个巨大的分歧
this is a huge, divisive issue for them.
这意味着  不管结果如何
Which means no matter what happens,
你们都会十分憎恨对方
there's gonna be a lot of resentment.
这种憎恨可能持续数年
Probably lasting for years...
无时无刻影响着
infecting every single moment
你们今后的关系
of the rest of their relationship.
因此  综上所述  还是罗宾说得对
So, in conclusion, I'm with Robin on this.
感谢支持
Thank you.
当晚  在我熟睡之际
That night,as I slept soundly...
巴尼  你在干嘛
Barney, what are you doing?
巴尼是谁
Who is this Barney?
我是约翰・克里福德・拉拉比
My name is John Clifford Larrabee,
阿卡迪亚酒店的设计师
architect of The Arcadian.
我来到你的梦中拜访你
And I am visiting you in a dream...
真的假的  感觉更像是
Really? 'Cause it feels more like
我那位租了件戏服
my insane friend renting a costume
就半夜闯进我公寓的疯子朋友
and breaking into my apartment in the middle of the night
这已经不是他第一次干这种事了
for what I wish I could say was the first time.
这就是个梦
Look, it's a dream, it is.
别那么较真  行吗
So just... okay?
西奥多
Theodore...
记住我的话
heed my words:
不要试图挽救阿卡迪亚
do not try to save The Arcadian.
巴尼  抽屉里有套套
Barney, there's condoms in the drawer.
拿了赶紧走人
Just take them and get out.
都说了我不是巴尼
I am not Barney...
哇  光线变色了
Whoa! Lighting change!
西奥多  阿卡迪亚酒店是座失败的建筑
Theodore, you know The Arcadian is a badly built,
在建筑史上毫无价值的老鼠窝
architecturally unimportant rat's nest
由一个值得竖起双拇指称赞的
designed by an overpaid,
薪酬过高  会抄袭的酒鬼设计的
plagiarizing ether addict with two thumbs.
正是在下
This guy.
好吧  我承认  它是个糟糕的建筑
Okay, yes, it's-it's a terrible building,
但就因为这个  我们就必须把它拆了吗
but... does that mean we have to knock it down?
我是说  它并没有影响任何人
I mean, it's not bothering anyone.
除了住在里面的人
Just anyone who lives in it.
或是看见它的人
Or looks at it.
又或是闻到它的人
Or smells it.
纽约的变化永不止步  西奥多
New York is never finished, Theodore.
她是位女士
She's a lady
只有为数不多的建筑师有机会与她共舞
only a handful of architects ever get to dance with.
别错过你的机会
Do not miss your turn.
阿卡迪亚必须得拆  是吗
The Arcadian has to go, doesn't it?
没错
Indeed.
你知道这等于把我的私人生活给毁了吧
You realize this kind of screws up my personal life.
房子越多  问题越多
Mo' buildings, mo' problems.
仿Notorious BIG单曲Mo' Money Mo' Problems
这是个梦  对吧
This is a dream, right?
巴尼  我发誓如果是你
Because, Barney, I swear to God, if that's you...
妈咪有魔力私物哦  泰德
Mommy's got Magic Lady Bits, Ted.
是梦  是梦
Dream! Dream!
那只是个梦
It was just a dream.
我知道有点晚
Hey. I know it's late, but, uh...
你想见面吗
you want to meet up?
你好  狮子先生
Hello, Mr. Lion.
功业盖物
"Look on my works,
强者折服
ye mighty, and despair"
出自雪莱的十四行诗《Ozymandias》1818
我就在这里
Hey, I met you right...
遇见你
...here.
是的  我就在这里
Right. And I mistook you
把你误认为妓女
for a prostitute right here.
如你所知  我姿色还在
As far as you know, I still could be one.
而你呢
Ah. And you,
我的好好先生  你已经欠了我一屁股债了哦
my good man, have run up quite a tab.
物有所值
Worth every penny.
好了
All right...
今天很开心
this was fun.
我要坐车回去了
I'm gonna take this cab.
明天是个大日子
Big day tomorrow.
我们得好好睡一觉
We need to get some sleep.
或者
And yet...
不了  睡觉吧
No, we should get some sleep.
但今晚很开心
But this was fun.
是啊
Yeah.
抬头看最后一眼  提醒我们
It's nice getting one last look
记住我们努力拯救的是什么  感觉真好
to remember what we're trying to save.
没错
Exactly.
你还好吗
You okay?
我很好  晚安
Yeah. Good night.
莫斯比先生  我将问你最后一遍
Mr. Mosby, I'm going to ask you one last time.
阿卡迪亚该成为地标建筑吗
Should The Arcadian be a landmark?
不  它不该成为地标建筑
No, it shouldn't be a landmark.
纽约有许多重要的建筑
There are a lot of important buildings in New York.
阿卡迪亚并不在此之列
The Arcadian isn't one of them.
抱歉打断一下
E-Excuse me,
我有个问题想问莫斯比先生
I have a question for Mr. Mosby.
如果他不认为
If he doesn't think
阿卡迪亚值得拯救  那这声音是谁的
The Arcadian's worth saving, then whose voice is this?
阿卡迪亚值得成为一个地标建筑
The Arcadian should be a landmark.
真的
It should.
它的狮子头是如此的有象征性
The lion head stonework is iconic.
我恨死了为巨人银行工作
I hate working for GNB.
他们是一群
They're a bunch of...
用生殖器思考的人
wieners and gonads.
我的老天爷
Oh, heavens!
我的上帝
My stars!
那是你的声音吗  莫斯比先生
Is that your voice, Mr. Mosby?
对  是我
Yeah, that's me.
这简直是一场恶梦
This is a nightmare.
真不敢相信她还留着那段录音
I can't believe she kept that tape.
地标保护委员会明天将会做出最终决定
The LPC's gonna come back with a decision tomorrow,
基于今天的表现
and based on today...
他们肯定会把那个该死的地方定为地标建筑
They're gonna landmark the hell out of that place.
是啊  我们马上就要变成无业游民
Yeah. We'll end up out of a job,
这全都归功于某个傻里傻气
all thanks to some stupid,
却有点威武的狮子头
only sort of awesome lion head.
你最好快点习惯那个狮子头
Better get used to that lion head.
从明天开始  它将永远在那屹立不倒
As of tomorrow, it's gonna be there till the end of times.
这全都归功于我那美妙又讨喜的押韵
And all because of my sweet, sweet rhymes.
我们该怎么办
What are we gonna do?
-我们应该买家酒吧  -我们真应该买家酒吧
- We should buy a bar. - We should totally buy a bar!
我们绝对应该买家酒吧
We should absolutely totally buy a bar!
这是目前唯一明智的主意了
It's really the only sensible idea right now.
准备好听我的想法了吗
Oh, oh, and ready?
这是主题酒吧
It's a theme bar.
把它布置成法庭
It's a courtroom.
-不错  -对
- Yes! - Ah!
酒吧的服务员要穿着性感的法官袍
Where the bartenders wear sexy judges' robes.
准了
I'll allow it!
这是唯一一个你一出现  就会获刑的法庭
The only court where you show up, then get served.
赞
Ho!
评判工作交给啤酒陪审团来完成
You're judged by a jury of your beers.
这主意不错
That's not bad.
你们都给我闭嘴
Just stop it!
没人要买酒吧
No one's buying a bar.
我们现在遇到了一点小难题
Right now we have a little problem.
要齐心协力想出解决的办法
Let's just think of a solution.
莉莉  结束了
Lily, it's over.
好人一败涂地
The good guys lost.
这可说不准  死党会为朋友插敌人两刀
I don't know, homegirl is pretty diabolical.
如果真有一个计划能让咱们脱离困境
If there is a plan that'll get us out of this,
肯定藏在这小脑袋里[butter churn亦有女性阴部之意]
it's somewhere inside this butter churn.
她会想出来的
She'll think of it.
我准备坐在这儿
I'm just gonna sit here...
等着灵光一闪那刻的降临
and watch it happen.
她想出来了
And she's got it!
莉莉  计划是什么
Lily, what's the plan?
最好是个好计划
Oh, this ought to be good.
于是莉莉告诉了我们她的计划
And then Lily told us her plan.
哇  真是好到不行不行的
Oh, this is good!
我们得马上去找亚瑟
We have to find Arthur right now.
这有这么难吗
What is so difficult about this?!
小拖船不到五分钟就做到了
Tugboat figured this out in, like, five minutes.
你果然是个次等货
This is bush league!
亚瑟  你好
Hey, Arthur!
小狗真可爱
Oh, cute dog!
不  我另一只狗小拖船才叫可爱
No! Tugboat, my other dog, that was a cute dog.
这个让人失望的小玩意  就是一便宜的仿货
This little disappointment is nothing but a cheap facsimile.
我实话实说
I said it!
我的爱是给那种
Yeah, my love is reserved for dogs
能听命令上厕所的狗
that go to the bathroom on command
而不是浪费我时间的狗
instead of wasting my time!
亚瑟  马修的妻子想到一个主意
Listen, Arthur, Marshall's wife has an idea
能让我们扭转大势  达到拆毁阿卡迪亚的目的
for how we can save not saving The Arcadian.
哦  他的妻子想到个主意
Oh, his wife has an idea.
让我告诉你何为妻子
Let me tell you about wives, okay?
她们不但离开你  还把你最好的朋友给带走了
They leave you and take your best friend with them.
这货不是小拖船
You're not Tugboat!
这货永远也成不了小拖船
You'll never be Tugboat!
亚瑟
Hey, Arthur?
我猜这狗也算可爱的一种吧
I guess this one's kind of cute or whatever.
那你的主意是什么
So... so what's the idea?
好的  先听完我的要求
Okay, first hear my demands.
一  不许辞掉泰德和巴尼
One,Ted and Barney keep their jobs.
二  当你们最后真能炸毁阿卡迪亚时
Two, when you guys do finally blow up The Arcadian,
要让他们俩其中一个按下那个按钮
one of them gets to push the button.
-我来  -我来
- Dibs. - Dibs.
好吧  到底是什么主意
Fine! What's the idea?
-这个嘛  -孩子们  因为法律原因
- Well... - Kids, for legal reasons,
我必须省略这部分故事
I have to skip this part of the story
直接跳到第二天晚上
and jump ahead to the next night,
地标保护委员会
as the Landmarks Preservation Commission
做出最后裁定
gave their verdict.
昨晚  全体委员进行了一次投票
Last night, this committee took a vote,
虽然我们最初都觉得
and while we have all felt from the very beginning that
阿卡迪亚酒店是
The Arcadian is,
一座难看的建筑
well, an eyesore...
在关于狮子头的石雕像方面
Mr. Mosby's surprising testimony
莫斯比先生却给出了出人意料的证词
about the lion's head stonework
这让我们别无选择  只好宣判它是
left us no choice but to declare it...
一座地标建筑
a landmark.
然而昨晚发生了件有趣的事
But then, something else happened last night.
就是那个狮子头石雕像
That same lion's head stonework...
消失了
...disappeared.
所以  这让我们的工作变得简单了
So...that makes our job a little easier.
动议否决
Motion denied.
苏伊
Zoey...
Zoey!
好吧  你还有什么好说的
All right, what do you have to say for yourself?
我不知道
I don't know.
可能有时  为了给更好的事物让路
Sometimes... things have to fall apart
有些事物不得不破碎
to make way for better things.
我们曲终人散
We're done here.
好了  你不必再隐藏了
Okay, you don't have to hold back anymore.
你现在可以告诉我  你对苏伊的真实想法
You may now say what you really think of Zoey.
我也不知道  关于那个狮子头或许她说得对
I don't know, she may have been right about the lion's head.
它让阿卡迪亚有一种帝王范的优雅
It gave The Arcadian a regal elegance.
重申一次  它跟我的羽绒被真的很搭
Then again, it goes really nice with my duvet.
希望我没用错螺丝刀[掉下来就完蛋了]
I hope I used the right screws.